<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Application xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/xmlwiki/DSA10/cw2meta.xsd">
    <student>
        <studentId>09019365</studentId>
        <hours>18</hours>
        <comment>This assignment was a challenge for me but it was very rewarding when each section of the site eventually came together to form a realistic web application, albeit a very small one with many limitations. I can see how it would be possible to scale the application and how adding more functionality could expand the scope, for example adding the functionality to not only report a missing object, but also a found object and a notification of a sighting of a found object. I found it difficult to start off with planning out the data model and thinking about which fields would need to be in which table and how they would join. Once this was set up though, I didn't find writing the PHP and SQL commands to be too much of a challenge because we have covered a lot of these subjects during the year. I feel that a main area for improvement for this site would be to make it more secure by adding validation to the forms and more robust by pulling out common sections of code that have been repeated in multiple pages and putting them into a common library folder. This would make my code more readable and more effiecient.</comment>
    </student>
    <WP1>
        <component>
            <title>Missing Children</title>
            <type>XML</type>
            <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/missing_children.xml</sourceURI>
            <purpose>Perceived data model of the missing children website.</purpose>
        </component>
    </WP1>
    <WP2>
        <component>
            <title>Lost Toys</title>
            <type>XML</type>
            <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/lost_toys.xml</sourceURI>
            <purpose>Data model of the missing budgies website.</purpose>
        </component>
    </WP2>
    <WP3>
        <WP3a>
            <component>
                <title>Home Page</title>
                <type>PHP</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/index.php</sourceURI>
                <purpose>The home page sets the purpose of the site and displays recently lost items for quick perusal.</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>functions.php</title>
                <type>PHP</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/missing_budgies/functions.txt</sourceURI>
                <purpose>Contains utility functions used throughout the site and connects to the MySQL database</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>RSS Feed Page</title>
                <type>PHP</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/missing_budgies/rss_feed.txt</sourceURI>
                <purpose>The RSS Feed page. Contains all code to generate the feed, pulling the data from the database.</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>SQL to generate database</title>
                <type>SQL</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/sql.txt</sourceURI>
                <purpose>SQL used to generate the database.</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>Test Data</title>
                <type>Text</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/sql.txt</sourceURI>
                <purpose>Test data for the database.</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>Report Missing Page</title>
                <type>PHP</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/report_missing.txt</sourceURI>
                <purpose>The page used to report a missing budgie. Contains both the HTML used to produce the form as well as all PHP to process the request and insert the data in to the database.</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>Report Sighting Page</title>
                <type>PHP</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/report_missing.txt</sourceURI>
                <purpose>The page to report a sighting of a missing budgie. Contains HTML and required PHP to process the request and insert the data in to the database.</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>Search Page</title>
                <type>PHP</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/searchresults.phps</sourceURI>
                <purpose>Contains the HTML and PHP for searching the database for a result.</purpose>
            </component>
            <component>
                <title>View Budgie Page</title>
                <type>PHP</type>
                <sourceURI>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~raenicho/dsa/viewdetails.phps</sourceURI>
                <purpose>Contains the HTML and PHP to view a specific budgie along with reportings of sightings.</purpose>
            </component>
        </WP3a>
    </WP3>
</Application>